<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on teh.su</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on teh.su</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 02:00:20 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>"INVALID OR CORRUPTED PACKAGE (PGP SIGNATURE)" FIX IN ARCH</title><link>/posts/fix-arch-corrupt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 02:00:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>/posts/fix-arch-corrupt/</guid><description>
Sometimes I get an error like such, “error: failed to commit transaction (invalid or corrupted package)” in Arch Linux when updating a package, recently it was cdrtools causing my pain.
To fix this, run the following, sudo pacman -S archlinux-keyring</description></item><item><title>Install Proxmox Without IPMI (OVH)</title><link>/posts/proxmox-without-ipmi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 05:34:09 -0600</pubDate><guid>/posts/proxmox-without-ipmi/</guid><description>
Usually you have the option to use IPMI and install your own OS on the Dedi that you ordered. With SoYouStart, that option cost money, about 30 dollars a day. So, in this we’ll go over how to install proxmox 6/7 using kvm.
The first step is to go to the SYS console and reboot the server into rescue mode. Once it is booted, you’ll receive the temp credentials which you can use to get root access to the machine.</description></item><item><title>Automated Postgres Backups using Docker</title><link>/posts/postgres-docker-backups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 04:37:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>/posts/postgres-docker-backups/</guid><description>
This section we’ll go over running backups for postgres running in docker.
A few things, since I am running rclone as the backend for the filesystem here, we can’t do hardlinks.
My docker image here, https://hub.docker.com/r/tehsu/docker-postgres-backup-local is built with a cp rather than a symlink.
I plan to add checks to see if hardlinks are available, if they are then we’d continue to use symlinks otherwise we’d need to copy the file.</description></item></channel></rss>